First Name: Leonardo

Last Name: Porto de Carvalho

Pós Graduação | Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Minas Gerais leonardomarcel.pc@gmail.com

This resume was automatically generated from: https://www.linkedin.com/in/leonardo-porto-de-carvalho-ab343a24

Summary

I'm a Software Engineer with experience in web software. In my professional time line, i worked both in elaboration steps, building software documentations, as a software construction developing solutions in Python. I Already worked in a software improvement process model MPS-BR, same a CMMI-SOFTWARE, resulting a level F (2009) maturity for a company that i worked, and after level G (2013). I love enjoy new experiences, learn with other and share my knowledge.

Experience

Software Engineer at XPD Soluções Tecnológicas April 2018 -

- * Python;
- * Django;
- * Django Rest Framework;
- * SGBD PostgreSQL;
- * Git, Gitlab.

Software Engineer at Capgemini

August 2014 - April 2018

- * Python com framework Django;
- * Django Rest Framework;
- * SGBD PostgreSQL;
- * Relatórios com Ireport;
- * Git, Gitlab, SVN

Software Developer at ADM Projetos e Consultoria

September 2011 - August 2014

Working with developing software solutions, make activities for software build, programing in Python and Django Framework.

Software Developer at Secretaria de Estado da Educação e do Esporte de Alagoas - SEEE-AL

September 2009 - August 2010

- * PHP
- * Mysql

Configuration Manager at Inform Sistemas LTDA

May 2009 - February 2014

Worked in a software quality process MPS-BR (Brazilian Software Process Improvement) witch resulting in a maturity certification level F (2009) and after Level C (2013).

Establishing and keeping the work products integrity through audit based in itens established by customer to be in compliance with Software Developer Reference Model by MPS.BR (MR-MPS-SW).

Education

Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Minas Gerais Pós Graduação, Arquitetura de Software Distribuído, 2019 -2021

CESMAC

Pós-graduação, Gestão de Projetos em Ti, Project Management, 2011 - 2013

CESMAC

Graduação, Análise de Sistemas, 2004 - 2008